（忆往昔）
睁开你的双眼 迪恩
Open your eyes, Dean.
我们一起对月长啸吧
And let's go take a howl at that moon.
天堂需要你的帮助
Heaven needs your help.
说吧
Anything.
丹尼尔和阿迪娜
Daniel and Adina.
得找到他们
They must be found.
他们必须被带回家
They must be brought home,
并受到责罚 这是为了所有人
and they must be punished for the sake of all.
好好想想
Think of it…
地狱之王 有迪恩·温彻斯特相助
The king of hell, Dean Winchester by his side.
我们一起统治 一起创建完美的地狱
Together we rule. Together we create the perfect hell.
我们之间萌生的友谊 永远不会结束
And all of this that's bloomed between us never ends.
别背对我
Hey! Don't turn your back on me!
你这是干什么
What do you think you're doing?
我想干什么干什么
Oh, whatever I want.
你是来找迪恩的
You're here for Dean.
我正要把他给你
I'm here to give him to you.
那小混蛋坏我生意
The little prat's bad for business.
他…不受控制 一定是因为血印
He's…uncontrollable. Must be the mark.
你的…小伙伴克劳力
Your, uh, pal Crowley…
出卖你了
Sold you out.
我们知道怎么治愈恶魔 记得吗
Look, we know how to cure demons. You remember that?
一点拉丁文 加上大量的血
Little latin, lot of blood.
现在你打算怎样 杀了我吗
So, what are you gonna do? Are you gonna kill me?
你是我哥哥
You are my brother.
我是来带你回家的
And I'm here to take you home.
你真以为那玩意会管用吗
You really think those are gonna work?
别动 结束了
Stop! It's over!
结束了
It's over, Dean.
（如今）
医生
Doctor.
神父
Father.
（人血）
不是吧
Really?
不管怎样
For whatever it's worth,
我拿的是你的血型的血
I got your blood type.
萨姆 我知道你想试着治好我
Sam, I know you think you're gonna try and fix me,
但你想过没有 或许我不想被治好
but did it ever occur to you that maybe I don't want to be fixed?
让我过自己的生活吧
Just let me go live my life.
我又不会打搅你
I won't bother you.
你在乎什么
What do you care?
我在乎什么
What do I care?
[咒语]
你以为我会像克劳力一样
You think I'm just gonna sit here like Crowley,
被你注射点血 就眼泪婆娑的吗
getting all weepy while you shoot me up?
去你的吧
Well, screw that.
我不想要这样
I don't want this.
这我看出来了
Yeah, I pretty much figured that out.
你根本不确定这能不能好使 对吧
You don't even know if this is gonna work, do you?
我体内的东西可不止
You know, I got a hell of a lot more running through me.
恶魔能量那么简单
than just demon juice.
该隐血印 了解
Mark of cain… got it.
没错
That's right.
坐稳了
Buckle up.
萨姆
Sammy…
你知道我讨厌打针
You know I hate shots.
我还讨厌恶魔呢
I hate demons.
我们血还多着呢
Look, we got a whole bunch more of these to go.
你可以让自己好过一点
You could make it a lot easier on yourself.
[邪恶力量 第10季第3集]
你还好吗
How are you holding up?
挺好的
Fine.
你嘴上这么说
You say you're fine,
但你看上去不太好
but you don't look fine.
人类就是这样
It's what the humans do.
他们嘴上装没事
They say they're fine,
即使我看上去不好
and even if I-I don't look it,
你也要说我气色不错 这样
you say I look well, and in that way,
我们就避免谈一件我们都无能为力的事
we avoid talking about something we can do nothing about.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我就是不明白萨姆·温彻斯特怎么能
I just can't see how Sam Winchester could ask you.
明知道你的状况 还让你大老远
to drive all this way to help with his brother,
开车去帮他哥哥
knowing your condition.
他不知道
He doesn't know…
你的借来的能量消耗得多严重 是吗
about how badly your borrowed grace is fading, does he?
他有些了解
He knows some.
他也不用多说
And he didn't have to ask.
这事上萨姆孤立无援
Sam is alone in this.
他想利用神圣化的血把迪恩
He's attempting to change Dean from demon to human.
从恶魔变回人类
with a cure of sanctified blood, but…
但这办法没有保证
there's no guarantee that will work.
如果不好使 那么迪恩就已经不在
If it doesn't, then Dean is gone,
那个恶魔必须被解决掉
and the demon must be dealt with.
我就是
I just…
担心你
I worry about you.
你说不定是在要我的命呢
For all you know, you could be killing me.
或者
Or…
你只是在耍我
you're just messing with me.
不管怎样 传说里没有关于
Either way, the lore doesn't say anything.
对血没有反应的案例
about exceptions to the cure.
传说
"The lore."
猎人 记录者
Hunters… men of letters.
都是扯淡
What a load of crap it all is.
没话可说吗
Oh, you got nothin'?
你想要我反驳你吗
You want me to debate you?
现在说话的根本不是真正的你
This isn't even the real you I'm talking to.
绝对是真正的我
Oh, it's the real me, all right.
新的真我
The new real me…
那个能看清现实的我
The me that sees things for what they really are.
温家双煞 行善积德 抗衡自然法则
Winchesters… do-gooders… fighting the natural order.
我告诉你吧
Let me tell you something…
我这种人 我们就是自然法则
guys like me, we are the natural order.
世界本就该如此
It's the way it was set up.
我这样的人 还是得尽力而为
Guys like me still got to do what we can.
别那么自大 萨姆
Don't be so full of yourself, Sammy.
依我看
'cause, see, from where I'm sitting,
我的变化
there ain't much difference.
和你的堕落没什么区别
from what I turned into to what you already are.
这话什么意思
And what exactly is that supposed to mean?
我知道你去找我的时候做了什么
I know what you did when you went looking for me.
我知道你做的多过分
I know how far you went.
克劳力都告诉我了
Crowley told me all about it.
我问问你
So, let me ask you…
我们俩究竟谁是魔头
…which one of us is really a monster?
开始想起来了
Starting to come back to you now?
我现在怎么办啊
What am I supposed to do now?
我的人生都结束了
It's like my life is over.
谢谢
Thank you.
贱人
Bitch.
我早该预料到的
I should've seen it coming.
为什么我从来都这么不顺啊
Why doesn't anything ever work out for me?
你好啊
Hey, there.
听上去
Sounds like, uh…
你最近不太好过啊
Things have been a little rough on you lately, huh?
不好过
Rough?
我老婆把我赶走了
My wife kicked me to the curb.
我们都4个月没做爱了
We haven't had sex for four months.
4个月啊
Four.
不过她可是没少做
Well, not that… not that she hasn't been having plenty…
是跟她保龄球队的一个男人
with a guy in her bowling league…
那人有纹身
Guy with tattoos.
我去上班 她就在餐桌上干他
Did him right there on the kitchen table while I was at work.
天呐 这太过分了
Man. That's, uh… that's cold.
我现在满心都是复仇
Now all I think of is revenge…
报复
Payback.
但这是做不到的
But that's not gonna happen.
那可未必啊
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
你或许是可以复仇的
It is possible that you can… have your revenge.
其实说起来
I mean, hell, it's possible.
你想要什么都行
you can have pretty much anything you want.
你想找到我和克劳力
You were trying to get a 20 on Crowley and me.
为此到处抓恶魔
from any demon you could snag.
但克劳力一心想躲起来
But Crowley didn't want to be found,
你即使召唤他 他也不来
and no one showed when you summoned.
但你还是想到了办法 不是吗 萨姆
But you find a way, didn't you, Sam?
好了 站在这儿
All right. Stand right here.
等我发话 就读出纸上的字
When I say so, read the words off the paper.
这样能行吗
A-are you sure about this?
没问题 相信我
Yeah. Trust me.
念吧
All right. Go ahead.
好的
Okay, um…
[咒语]
念得不对
Tati! Voluntati!
[咒语]
谁召唤我 什么目的
Who summons me, and for what purpose?
杀了我妻子
Kill my wife…
莱斯特
Lester!
我的灵魂就归你了
…and my soul is yours.
- 别 - 成交
- Don't! - Done.
不要
No!
你本希望能在交易完成前及时制止
You would have liked to have gotten there before the deal went down,
但你其实并不在乎可怜的老莱斯特 是吧
but you didn't really care about poor ol' Lester, did you?
再来一次
Why don't we try that again?
没人知道克劳力和你哥哥在哪
Nobody knows where Crowley and your brother are.
他们消失不见了
They're off the radar!
要杀我就动手吧
Kill me if you want to!
我不知道别的了
That's all I know.
我没什么好跟你说的
I got nothing for you.
而你却让那个可怜虫出卖了自己的灵魂
And you made that poor son of a bitch sell his soul.
告诉你一声 莱斯特是我亲手结果的
Oh, and so you know, I killed Lester myself.
他老婆嫁给纹身男了
And that wife of his married the tattooed guy.
我本意不是…
I never meant…
谁管你本意如何呢
Who cares what you meant?!
我们本以为我们和
That line that we thought was so clear.
猎物之间有条清晰的界线
between us and the things that we hunted.
但其实没那么清晰 是吧
ain't so clear, is it?
你可能比我还烂
You might actually be worse than me.
你利用了一个处于人生低谷的男人
I mean, you took a guy at his lowest, used him,
他为此丢了性命和灵魂
and it cost him his life and his soul.
真厉害
Nice work.
我问你 萨姆
Let me ask you this, Sammy.
如果这不好使
If this doesn't work…
我们都清楚你要怎么处置我 对吧
We both know what you got to do to me, right?
你下得了手吗 萨姆
You got the stomach for that, Sam?!
你被控叛国罪
You stand accused of high treason.
带下去
Take her away.
这又是怎么了
So, what's this, then?
天呐 又是一份等我签字的文件
Oh, goody… something else to sign.
自此以后 立刻生效…
"Henceforth and forthwith…
为促进
"For the furtherance.
并方便 管理…
and expedience and regulation and…"
嗯
Yeah.
行啊
Sure.
陛下 请愿者在苦苦等候
Majesty, supplicants await without.
等什么
Without what?
您的接见
Outside.
让他们等吧
Let them wait.
他们已经等很久了
They've waited a long time.
这里是地狱 就得等
It's hell. You wait.
就是这样
It's what you do.
你怎么还不走
You're still here.
我有天使卡西迪奥的新消息
I have an update on the angel Castiel.
他的能量似乎在消退
His grace seems to be fading.
他越来越弱了
He's losing strength.
如果有这个想法
If one were so inclined,
那么现在是干掉他的合适时机
this would be a propitious time for one to eliminate him.
你指谁
"One"?
您 陛下
You, sire.
借来的能量的确用不久
Borrowed grace does have a puny shelf life.
卡西迪奥应该仔细阅读警告标签
Castiel should have read the warning label.
跟住他
Follow him.
把他的削弱情况时刻报告我
And keep me informed as to his decline.
怎么回事
What's going on here?
- 你觉得呢 - 在我的床上搞
- What's it look like? - In my bed?!
- 混蛋 - 贱人
- Jerk. - Bitch.
- 守住 守住 - 闭嘴吧
- Knock it down. Knock it down! - Stop talking!
你要丢球了
You're bodging it!
地狱之王 有迪恩·温彻斯特相助
The king of hell, Dean Winchester by his side.
我们一起统治 一起创建完美的地狱
Together, we rule. Together, we create the perfect hell.
王上
Great one?
陛下
Your majesty?
您还好吧
Are you…all right?
我在回想辉煌岁月
I was thinking of better days.
是啊 您的休假
Yes… your sabbatical.
什么
My what?
我们当时很担心
Uh, we were worried, of course.
您跟温家哥哥的事故
Your misadventure with the older Winchester.
倍受揣测
was quite the topic of speculation.
请恕我大胆
Uh, if you'll forgive my boldness…
我可以给您做伴
I could now be your wingman.
是嘛
Could you?
我也喜欢逛派对
I, too, love to party,
我也喜欢女人
and I do love the ladies.
还有经典摇滚
and the classic rock 'n' roll.
最重要的是 我可以跟您一起玩乐
Most importantly, I can debauch by your side.
又不会出丑
without being a personal embarrassment.
您会看到我的价值的
You'll see what I'm worth.
我已经看出来了
Oh, I can see already.
还有谁有话说吗
Anyone else care to comment?
抱歉 我又拐错弯了
Sorry. I…missed another turn.
我不知道主路在哪
I have no idea where the main road is.
这些东西
These things…
都那么局限 原始
they're so confining and primitive.
真是…
It's…
你的情况越来越糟了 是吗
It's getting worse, isn't it?
卡西迪奥 我们不能再回避明摆着的事了
Castiel, it's time we stopped avoiding the obvious.
我们都清楚要怎么解决你的困境和这种局面
You and I both know how to fix this… both you and the situation.
我不能去割破哪个天使的喉咙 盗取那人的能量
I will not slit some angel's throat and steal its grace.
你也别开口了
Before you say it,
我们是绝不会去求梅塔特隆的
we definitely are not going begging to Metatron.
那帮助你的朋友
What about helping your friend.
把脱逃的天使送回天堂呢
and sending the rogue angels back to heaven?
你想要坚守原则 等死
Your preference to die for your principles…
这虽然高尚 但毫无意义
it's very noble, but it is meaningless.
那你就继续使命
Then you carry on.
我一个人不够
I'm not enough.
有时候 尽全力就够了
Sometimes, enough is whatever you have.
萨姆
Sam?
小卡
Cass.
你还来吗
Hey, are you still coming?
就几小时的路了
I'm a few hours away.
治疗有效果吗
Is the treatment working?
不 不太好
No, not very well.
跟克劳力当时的情况不同
Look, i-it's not like it was with Crowley.
迪恩很痛苦
Dean's in pain.
他真的很痛苦
I mean, he's in bad pain.
他好像要撑不住了
I-It's like he's barely holding on.
小卡…我说不定是在害死他
Cass… I might be killing him.
有这种可能
It might be.
所以呢…
So…
怎么 我该停手吗
What? Should I stop?
然后又怎么办呢
And do what?
他又不是被附身
He's not possessed.
驱魔也没用
Exorcism is out of the question.
净化血仪式是我知道的唯一办法
The ritual of purified blood is the only treatment I know.
小卡 你没听到我说什么了吗
Cass, did you not hear what I just said?
我可能是在害死我哥哥
I could be killing my brother.
萨姆 他不是你哥哥了 至少现在不是
Sam, he's not your brother … at least not now.
你必须做好准备…
You have to be prepared for …
杀死我哥哥
Killing my brother.
我会尽快赶过去
I'll be there as soon as I can.
好的 好吧
Yeah, all right.
我会…给你留门的
I'll, uh, I'll leave the entry unlocked for you.
你…尽快
Just… hurry.
迪恩 醒醒啊
Dean! Come on!
- 回来 - 不要
- Come back. - No.
回到我身边来 你在吗
Come back to me. You there?
迪恩 你还好吗
Dean, you okay?
还好 假如你…
Yeah, if you…
认为血液沸腾 快被汗淹死 是「还好」的话
consider drowning in your own sweat while your blood boils okay.
听着 我不能停手
Look, I can't stop doing this.
你当然可以停手
Sure you can.
你就停下就好
You just stop.
如今试图找回你哥哥已经毫无意义了
There's no point in trying to bring your brother back now.
我会把他找回来的
Oh, I will bring him back.
实际上 你…
In fact, your, uh,
满心愧疚 承受重担的哥哥
guilt-ridden, weight-of-the-world bro.
已经失踪蛮长一段时间了
has been M.I.A. for quite some time now.
但我挺喜欢这副新面目的
But I'm loving the new model …
懒散的 刻薄的迪恩
lean, mean Dean.
是啊
Right.
你发现我试着尽量远离你了吗
You notice I tried to get as far away from you as possible?
远离你的牢骚 你的抱怨
Away from your whining, your complaining.
我选择了地狱之王 抛弃了你
I chose the king of hell over you.
说不定我只是…
Maybe I was just…
厌倦了当你的保姆
tired of babysitting you.
厌倦了整天要救你出火坑
or always having to yank your lame ass out of the fire.
救了一辈子了
since forever.
也说不定…
Or maybe …
是因为想到 要不是因为你
maybe it was the fact that my mother would still be alive.
我妈妈可能还活着
if it wasn't for you.
想到你的存在
That your very existence.
夺走了我的生活 榨干了我的生命
sucked the life out of my life.
这不是我哥哥在说话
This isn't my brother talking.
你从来就没有过哥哥…
You never had a brother …
他不过是你软弱的借口
just an excuse for not manning up.
你猜怎么着
But guess what.
我放弃
I quit.
不行 你不能
No. No, you don't.
你不能放弃
You don't get to quit.
这个家里不允许放弃
We don't get to quit in this family.
我们一直以来就只有这个家了
This family is all we have ever had!
这样的话 我们就一无所有了
Well, then, we got nothin'.
你会对爸爸说这种话吗
Would you say that to dad?
爸爸
Dad?
这位才厉害呢
Oh, there's a prize.
这男人给我们洗脑
Here's a man who brainwashed us.
让我们浪费生命 为他的必败之战奋斗
into wasting our lives fighting his losing battle.
你这是在逞男子气概吗
Is this you manning up?
我这是在把你这混蛋拉出火坑
This is me yanking your lame ass out of the fire.
不用谢
You're welcome.
你强迫他人与阿比顿结盟
You have coerced others into aligning with Abaddon.
你散播谣言 质疑挑战
You've spread rumors and fostered doubt.
王权的实力和威仪
as to the competence and authority of the crown.
叛国罪
Guilty of treason.
判处死刑
The sentence is death.
还有谁想背叛我吗
Anyone else hungry to betray me?
下一个
Next.
你的罪名是…反正有罪
You're guilty of…something,
不管是什么 反正我不能容忍
which I won't tolerate, whatever it was.
你将被…
You are condemned to…
够了 停
Stop! Stop!
够了
Stop?
你不能这样
You cannot do this.
你没长眼吗 我当然可以 我已经做了
Weren't you watching? 'course I can. I just did.
你就打算这么统治吗
This is your idea of ruling?
对
Yes.
我们为了你杀人 虐待人
We've killed and tortured for you,
窃取灵魂 摧毁生命
stolen souls, destroyed lives,
为博你赏识吃尽苦头
tempted and tormented with distinction.
而我们得到的奖赏是什么
And for all this, what's our reward?
一记响亮的耳光
A slap in the face.
那是什么
What is it?
你说走就走 饮血狂欢
You disappear, binge on blood,
还差点有了人性
approach the edge of becoming human.
更雪上加霜的是
And the salt in the wound…
你跟你的小男宠迪恩·温彻斯特一起跑了
you run off with your boy toy, Dean Winchester,
现在他成了杀人狂
and now he's running amok,
你根本控制不了他 还有这王国
and you can't control him or the kingdom.
他在干什么啊
What's he doing?
你辜负了我们的忠诚
You've squandered our loyalty.
你想怎样
What will you do?
反正不要活在你创造的地狱里
Not live in the hell you've made.
是圣油
It's holy oil!
退后 退后
Get back! Get back!
没想到啊
Did not see that coming.
汉娜
Um, Hannah.
你知道 我们走的这条路非常危险
You know, this… this road we're on, it's… it's dangerous.
明白
All right.
我们不能迷路
We can't afford to lose our way.
我知道 地图的事很抱歉
I know that. I'm sorry about the map.
绝不能绕路
No detours of any kind.
卡西迪奥 如果你又是想
Castiel, if these are metaphors.
像人类那样用隐喻跟我交流
and you're attempting another human communication,
没用的
it isn't working.
我只想说这任务至关重要
I'm just trying to say that this mission is everything.
我知道
I know that.
去找迪恩 去追捕逃脱天使
Getting to Dean and hunting these rogues…
我现在能量不足 所以我
I… I'm not at full capacity, so I…
我们 一定要专注
We n-need total focus.
像激光一样 明白
Like a laser. Got it.
我跟人类相处了很长时间
Just…I've been around humans for long enough to see…
我知道分心有多容易
how easily distractions occur.
「分心」
"Distractions."
一切的情绪 感情
Emotions…feelings…
都是危险的诱惑
They're dangerous temptations.
多像《圣经》说的啊 卡西迪奥
How very biblical, Castiel.
我并不是想不近人情
I don't mean to be unkind.
你并不需要友善
You don't need to be kind.
我…
I just…
我是想明确一下我们的首要目标
I'm trying to keep our priorities clear.
那不用担心
Not to worry, then.
我很清楚我的首要目标 还有你的
I am very clear on my priorities. And yours.
有人吗
Hello?
久违了
Hey, there.
我追踪你们好几天了
I've been tracking you for days.
你们会为你们的所作所为受到惩罚
You will be punished for what you did.
丹尼尔的死 是个意外 阿迪娜
Daniel's death … that was unintentional, Adina.
我觉得你明白
I feel you know this.
意外
Unintentional?
你杀了他
You killed him!
来真的
Seriously?
杀了我吧 放她走
Just… kill me. But let her go.
住手
Stop.
「住手」 「杀了我」 好多建议
"Stop." "Kill me." I mean, so many suggestions,
真不知道该怎么做
I don't know what to do.
我知道我会杀了你 卡西迪奥
I know … I will kill you, Castiel,
但会很慢 很慢
But very, very slowly.
这样 你的小甜心就可以观赏了
So your … your honeybunch can watch.
怎么样
Sound good?
嘿 伙计
Hey, champ.
看看你
Look at you.
像被车碾过的动物一样
Talk about roadkill.
很好 汉娜 痛苦吧
Attagirl, Hannah. Suffer.
就像我的丹尼尔被你们杀死前那样
Just like my Daniel suffered before you killed him.
丹尼尔的死不怪我 怪你们自己
Daniel's death isn't on my head. It's on yours.
我们什么都没做
We did nothing.
我们只想独自生活
We wanted nothing but to be left alone.
你们杀了个天使 必须为此付出代价
You killed an angel. You had to answer for it.
一个要把我们强行拖回你们的天堂的天使
An angel who would have hauled us back to that heaven of yours.
你们一开始就该放过我们
You should have left us alone.
够了吧
And that will do.
你们为什么就不能像大家想象的那样
Why can't you people just sit on clouds and play harps,
坐在云端弹竖琴呢
like you're supposed to?
出来吧 萨姆
Come on, Sammy!
不想和哥哥玩玩吗
Don't you want to hang out with your big brother?
共享一点欢乐时光
Spend a little quality time?
别傻了
Don't be an idiot.
这是她的 但她正要杀你女朋友
Yes, it's hers, but she was killing your girlfriend.
你自己没动手
Your hands are clean.
我讨厌这么说
Much as it pains me to say this,
但你死了对我没好处
you're useless to me dead.
你欠我的
You owe me.
你为什么帮我
Why did you help me?
纯粹是利益需要
Purely business.
你离温家兄弟俱乐部会所只有5英里远
Since you're 5 miles away from the Winchesters' clubhouse,
我猜你们一定正往那儿赶吧
I can only surmise that you're headed there.
而迪恩的事很棘手
and that Dean has become a handful.
他变成恶魔后 除了给我添堵 毫无益处
Having him as a demon has caused me nothing but grief.
去解决这问题吧
Fix the problem.
你应该知道 最坏的情况
You realize … worse comes to worst,
是得杀了他
that means killing him.
我不是多愁善感的人
I'm not sentimental.
聪明 萨姆
Smart, Sam.
封锁地堡
Locking the place down.
门打不开 我明白
Doors won't open. I get it.
但关键是
But here's the thing.
我不想离开
I don't want to leave.
直到我找到你为止
Not till I find you.
萨姆
Sammy!
这样对你更不妙了
You're just making this worse for yourself, man!
顺便说一句
Oh, by the way,
我能逃脱都怪你
you can, uh…blame yourself for me getting loose.
你给我注入的血液 让我更有人性
All that blood you pumped into me to make me human … well.
我越不像恶魔 手铐作用就越小
The less demon I was, the less the cuffs worked.
而恶魔陷阱
And that devil's trap …
我直接能走过去
Well, I just walked right across it.
它虽然厉害
It smarted.
但是
But still…
这才像话
Yeah, that's more like it.
这就是你的大招吗
That's your big move?
听我说 迪恩
Listen to me, Dean!
我们要成功了 好吗
We were getting close, okay?
我知道你还在
I know you're still in there somewhere.
让我完成治疗吧
Just let me finish the treatments.
迪恩
Dean?
你说得好像我想被治愈似的
You act like I want to be cured.
就我而言 我喜欢这病
Personally, I like the disease.
迪恩 住手
Dean! Stop that!
我不想对你用刀
Look, I don't want to use this blade on you!
这对你来说可太糟了
That sucks for you, doesn't it?
因为你真是这么想的
'cause you really mean that.
如果你从那房间出来
Look, if you come out of that room,
我就别无选择了
I won't have a choice!
你当然有
Sure you will!
而且我知道你会怎么选择
And I know which one you'll make.
不是吗 萨姆
Isn't that right, Sammy?
但你瞧 是这样的
But, see… here's the thing.
我很幸运 我非常幸运
I'm lucky. Oh, hell, I'm blessed.
因为 我身体内还留有足够的魔性
'cause there's just enough demon left in me.
杀死你 根本不需要犹豫
that killing you ain't no choice at all.
萨姆
Sammy?
来啊 萨姆
Come on, Sammy!
我们一起喝杯啤酒 聊一聊
Let's have a beer, talk about it.
我玩够了
I'm tired of playing.
我们结束游戏吧
Let's finish this game!
瞧你啊
Well…look at you.
动手啊
Do it.
就看你的了
It's all you.
结束了
It's over.
迪恩 结束了
Dean, it's over.
结束了
It's over.
我们到底在干什么 小卡
What the hell are we doing to him, Cass?
我给了他那么多血
I mean, even after I gave him all that blood,
他还是说不想被治愈
he still said he didn't want to be cured,
不想做人类
that he didn't want to be human.
我能理解他
Well… I see his point.
只有人类才能真正感受快乐 但是
You know, only humans can feel real joy, but…
同样也有沉重的痛苦
also such profound pain.
这样更容易些
This is easier.
你们看起来很担心
You look worried, fellas.
欢迎回来 迪恩
Welcome back, Dean.
（驱魔指导）
他怎么样
How's he doing?
还有点迷迷糊糊
He's, uh… he's still a little out of it,
但我觉得好多了
but better, I think.
我觉得整件事
I mean, I think this whole thing …
血液治疗 这一切
The blood cure and the… all of it …
- 真的让他很累 - 是啊
- Really wrecked him, you know? - Yeah.
从好的方面说 他又饿了
On the plus side, he's hungry again,
所以我要去给他拿一大袋垃圾食品
so I'm just gonna go pick him up a big ol' bag of crap food.
然后亲自填饱他
and stuff it in his face myself.
- 你能帮我盯着点吗 - 好的
- You mind keeping an eye? - Yeah.
- 萨姆 - 嗯
- Sam? - Yeah?
你知道 解决了一个问题
You realize … one problem is solved,
但还有一个问题
but one still remains.
迪恩不再是恶魔 这是没错
Dean is no longer a demon. That's true.
但他还有该隐的血印
But the mark of Cain … that, he still has,
那迟早会是麻烦
and sooner or later, that's gonna be an issue.
你知道吗 小卡 我很累了
You know what, Cass? I'm beat, man.
一次一场战斗 好吗
One battle at a time, you know?
我去给我哥哥拿点胆固醇食物
So I'm just gonna go grab my brother some cholesterol.
然后我要把自己灌醉
And then I'm gonna get drunk.
进来
Yeah.
你看起来很糟糕
You look terrible.
偶尔说说谎不会要你命的
You know, it wouldn't kill you to lie every now and again.
是不会 我只是
No, it wouldn't kill me. I just…you …
算了吧
Forget it.
而你呢
Well, you, on the other hand, you…
看起来很不错
Looking good.
你又回来啦
So…are you back?
至少暂时是
At least temporarily.
说来话长 克劳力 偷来的能量
Yeah, it's a long story … Crowley, stolen grace.
外面汽车里有个女人
There's a female outside in the car.
下次吧
Another time.
谢谢你及时帮忙
Well, thank you for, um… stepping in when you did.
萨姆怎么说 他要离婚吗
What does Sam say? Does he want a divorce?
我确定萨姆知道
I'm sure Sam knows.
不论你说了什么 做了什么
that whatever you said or what you did,
那都不是真正的你
that wasn't really you.
反正不全都是你
It certainly wasn't all you.
我想杀了他 小卡
I tried to kill him, Cass.
迪恩 你们俩经历了那么多
Dean, you two have been through so much.
你们是兄弟
Look, you're brothers.
想用锤子杀了他 还不至于会
It'd take a lot more than trying to kill Sam with a hammer.
把他逼走
to make him want to walk away.
你知道我们的生活得糟到什么地步才会这样
You realize how screwed up our lives are that even makes sense?
我很高兴你来了
I'm glad you're here, man.
也许你该先休息一阵
Hey, maybe you should, um…take some time.
恢复一下 再投入工作
before you get back to work … allow yourself to heal.
这
It's, uh…
怎么说呢 时机也许正合适
I don't know. Timing might be right.
天堂和地狱 似乎都恢复了秩序
Heaven and hell … they seem reasonably back in order.
外面很平静
It's quiet out there.
（俄克拉荷马州 塔尔萨）